█
人人影视 原创翻译  双语字幕
See you in 30.
30分钟后见
Kel. Kel, Kel.
小凯  小凯  小凯
I missed you this morning.
今早我没见到你
Thought we had a shift together.
我们不是一起轮班吗
Sorry. Something came up.
抱歉  我有点事
You still want to do those shifts with me?
你还想跟我一起轮班吗
It's okay if you don't.
如果不想  也没关系
Next one. I promise.
下次一定  我保证
Kel.
小凯
Do you...
你
Do you wanna talk about it?
你想谈谈吗
Nothing to talk about.
没什么好谈的
Come on. Everyone -- pull!
大家一起  拉
Hey. Going somewhere?
你要出门吗
We need to get our horses back.
我们得找回马
You see the east wall when you came in?
你进来时看见东墙了吗
I did.
看见了
You were marked down to help today.
你今天该帮忙的
Looks like you've got a crew already.
你似乎已经有一队人了
Well, you were gone all morning.
你一早都不见人影
We started without you.
我们就先开工了
I'm sorry, Aaron. I can't today.
对不起  亚伦  我今天没法帮你
Because you're tracking horses
因为你在追踪一群
that you have almost no hope of catching?
几乎没希望抓到的马吗
You know, Daryl and I went down that road before.
达里尔和我之前也这样做过
Didn't work out so well for Buttons.
最后也没抓到巴顿斯
We're almost out of MREs,
我们的口粮快没了
and the fields are a joke --
庄稼地就是个笑话
And our walls are about to fail.
我们的墙要不行了
Well, if we don't get those horses,
如果我们找不到马
we're not gonna be able to move anything heavier
我们就没法搬运比一袋粮食
than a sack of grain.
更重的东西
Or go out far enough to scavenge anything,
也没法去远方搜刮物资
and we're all gonna starve to death.
我们都会饿死的
So I'll be back in a few hours.
我几小时后回来
I'm hungry, too.
我也很饿
Do you ever worry about your mom when she goes away?
你妈妈出去时  你会担心吗
I'm used to it.
我都习惯了
Grown-ups are always running off doing things.
大人总是会出去办事
"Promise I'll see you soon.
"我保证会很快回来
Love you."
爱你哦"
They used to say that kind of stuff in the olden times, right?
在旧时代他们常说那种话  对吗
They can't promise it now, but they say it anyways.
他们现在没法保证  但还是这样说
They don't want us to think they're never coming back.
他们不希望我们认为他们再也回不来了
It's supposed to make us feel better.
那些话是为了让我们好受些
They say it to make themselvesfeel better.
他们是为了让自己好受些
Still...
不管怎样
my mom always comes back.
我妈妈总是会回来
Yeah.
是啊
Dang it.
可恶
Lord, you are my refuge and my strength...
上帝  你是我的避难所  我的力量源泉
My refuge and my strength...
我的避难所  我的力量源泉
My refuge...
我的避难所
Alden.
奥尔登
Maggie.
玛姬
Jesus.
天啊
Let me see?
让我看看
Sure thing, boss.
行  老大
That good, huh?
这么惨吗
You think you can walk?
你可以走路吗
Not gonna know until we try.
试试才知道
You're not seriously thinking that we keep going.
你不会真觉得我们要继续前进吧
They'll be back. We gotta keep moving.
他们会再来的  我们得继续前进
Alright, wait. What exactly is the plan here?
好吧  等等  现在的计划到底是什么
The plan doesn't change.
计划不变
We need that food.
我们需要那些食物
We get to the radio tower, find the supply house,
我们去无线电塔  找到补给屋
and wait for the others.
然后等待其他人
And what if the others are dead?
如果其他人死了呢
Listen, I know theatrics.
我了解戏剧效果
Those people, they just told us
那些人刚告诉了我们
exactly how insane they are.
他们到底有多疯狂
We can't be on a road.
我们不能走大路
We can't be on any road that they could use.
我们不能走任何他们可能走的路
It's a shit plan.
这是个糟糕的计划
Then you tell me a better one
那你告诉我一个更好的
that doesn't starve us all.
不会让我们所有人饿死的计划
Right.
我就知道
I am on your side, Maggie.
我是站在你这边的  玛姬
Then help me with him.
那就帮我带他走
2, 3, go.
二  三  起
No.
不行
Not unless you want Coco tripping the light fantastic.
除非你想让可可神魂颠倒
Yeah, but just for like a week, tops, right?
但最多只会持续一周  对吧
- You good? - Yeah.
-你没事吧  -没事
Yeah, it's just that Gabriel's on a mission,
只是加百利在执行任务
and I'm over being stuck in the house.
而我被困在家里
Why? What're you guys doing?
怎么了  你们在做什么
Wait.
等等
Damn it!
该死
Fourth time's the charm.
第四次准有好运气
Let's get a move on.
我们继续吧
You okay?
你没事吧
I'll be better when this is done.
等抓到马就没事了
I've been having dreams about Abraham recently.
我最近一直在做关于亚伯拉罕的梦
Yeah?
是吗
Yeah, he's trying to tell me something.
是的  他想告诉我某件事
I know it's something important, something I'm supposed to do.
我知道那是重要的事  我应该做的事
But I can't hear him most of the time,
但大部分时候我都听不见他
and just when I'm about to...
就当我快听见时
he, um -- he gets shot in the head.
他就被爆头了
Well, that's dark.
真阴暗
Yeah, I don't know why I just told you that.
是啊  我不知道我为什么告诉你
No, I get it.
不  我懂的
It used to freak me out,
以前这会让我恐慌
but now I think it's a message for us, for Alexandria.
但现在我觉得这是一条给我们和亚历山大的信息
What do you think he's trying to say?
你觉得他想说什么
I don't know.
我不知道
You know, if a horse lets you touch its ear,
如果马让你摸它的耳朵
it means it trusts you.
就代表它信任你
I read that once.
我读到过
You think we'll get them back?
你认为我们能把它们抓回来吗
Horses are wild creatures.
马是野性的动物
You never know.
很难说
It's 2 miles. It's further than I thought.
有两英里  比我想的要更远
We better get moving.
那就快走吧
Holding your hand's not gonna help me walk any faster.
牵着你的手并不会帮我走快一点
Yeah? Does the thought of one of those things
是吗  那想到那些行尸会撕下你的脸
ripping your face off do it for you?
能帮你走快点吗
If you're scared, why don't you
如果你害怕  为什么
make yourself useful and go kill 'em?
不发挥下作用  去杀死它们
Really? So we're just gonna go towards the screaming?
真的吗  我们要朝着尖叫声走吗
Cool.
行吧
Agatha!
阿加莎
Maggie. It's Duncan.
玛姬  邓肯出事了
Duncan.
邓肯
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
For all of it.
为所有事
Why?
为什么
We were good.
我们之前过得很好
We were lucky.
我们很幸运
For a little while.
持续了一小段时间
Make sure she gets home.
确保她平安回家
Promise.
答应我
This way.
这边走
No.
不
It can't be.
不可能
It's okay.
没事的
We'll keep looking for the rest.
我们继续找其它的马
They'll stay close to the water.
它们会待在水源附近
Not if it's full of corpses they won't.
如果到处是尸体它们就不会了
Carol, it's getting late.
卡萝尔  天色晚了
She's right.
她说得对
We don't have to do this right now.
我们没必要现在去找
Let's come back tomorrow.
我们明天再回来
No, Alexandria needed these horses yesterday.
不  亚历山大昨天就需要这些马
Carol...
卡萝尔
Let's go home.
我们回家吧
We'll try again.
我们再试试
Next time.
下一次
Maybe not.
也许不用了
Dope.
真酷
They're headed towards the dairy farm.
它们直奔奶牛场了
- And? - The dairy farm's got paddocks.
-所以呢  -奶牛场有围场
We can pen them in.
我们可以把马关进去
Come on. Let's go.
快  我们走吧
Easy now. Easy now.
别紧张  别紧张
Drop the lassos.
放下套索
Why?
为什么
Just do it.
照做就是
They're not running.
它们没跑
I think they want to come home.
我觉得它们想回家了
Though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death,
我虽然行过死荫的幽谷
I will fear no evil, for thou art with me.
也不怕遭害  因为你与我同在
You move slower than I thought you would.
你比我预想得来得更慢
Don't be scared.
别害怕
I'm not.
我不怕
We have been blessed.
我们受到了保佑
I...
我
I have been blessed.
我受到了保佑
You have a funny definition of blessed.
你对保佑的定义真有趣
But it is you who has come for me.
但来取我命的人是你
Will you pray for me?
你会为我祷告吗
You tried to kill my friends.
你想杀掉我的朋友们
Yes.
是的
And they tried to kill me.
他们也想杀掉我
Pray for me.
为我祷告
Even your enemies deserve that much.
即便是你的敌人也应如此
I thought you were a man of God.
我以为你是信奉上帝的人
God isn't here anymore.
上帝已经不在了
Twice as many as before.
是之前的两倍多
We need to rethink your plan, Maggie.
我们得重新考虑下你的计划  玛姬
You're a free man, Negan. You wanna go?
你是自由的  尼根  你想走吗
Go.
走吧
I can help you.
我能帮你
You know, your friends, they trusted me.
你知道的  你的朋友们  他们信任我
You were gone for a long time.
你离开了很长时间
Things change. People change.
事情会变  人会变
No.
不
Maybe you've got them fooled, but not me.
也许你骗过了他们  但没骗过我
Stop pretending you're one of us, Negan.
不要再装作你是我们的一员了  尼根
Maybe you even believe it.
你可能连自己都信了
But you're probably as good at lying to yourself
但也许你不仅擅长骗别人
as you are to everybody else.
也一样擅长骗自己
You okay, Maggie?
你没事吧  玛姬
Yeah.
没事
I can handle Negan.
我能处理好尼根
I wasn't talking about Negan.
我说的不是尼根
This can't be what you thought you'd be coming home to.
这应该不是你想象中回家后的情形
It can't be what you told Hershel he'd see.
应该也不是你告诉赫谢尔他会看到的样子
You know, not much surprises me anymore.
你知道的  没有什么事情能让我再惊讶了
Except Hilltop.
除了山顶寨
It's not the place I told Hershel about.
我和赫谢尔讲的不是那样的地方
Hold on a sec.
等等
You know, I'm not sure much surprises him anymore, either.
我也不知道还有什么事情会让他惊讶
You'll build it back up,
你会把它重新建起来的
better than it was before.
比以前更好
We will.
我们会的
Sure.
好的
We'll get it done.
我们会做到的
At least by the time that Adam is old enough to remember.
至少那个时候  亚当就能记事了
I leave for one minute, and you're raising a kid.
我才离开了一小会  你就养了一个孩子
Maggie, if I, uh...
玛姬  如果我
We'll start when we get back, okay?
我们回去再说  好吗
The good news is, he lives in Alexandria, so...
好消息是  他住在亚历山大  所以
small wins.
小小的胜利
What the hell?
搞什么
This way.
这边
Come on!
快来
Let's go.
我们走
I got him.
我帮他
Agatha!
阿加莎
- Go! Just go! - No! Come on!
-走  快走  -不  不要
- Run! - No!
-快走  -不
Agatha, no!
阿加莎  不
No! Get off!
不  放手
No! No! No! No! No!
不  不  不
Look! They're back!
看  她们回来了
They've got the horses!
她们找回马了
Oh, my God!
天啊
I'll go get Aaron.
我去叫亚伦
Alright, I'm out.
好  我走了
Bye.
拜
Very good boy.
好孩子
Hey, Carol.
卡萝尔
Can we talk?
能聊聊吗
Yeah, sure.
当然
I know what you're doing, and I want you to stop.
我知道你在做什么  我要你停手
Sorry?
什么
You're giving Kelly false hope.
你给了凯利虚假的希望
I-I don't understand.
我不懂
Yes, you do.
你懂
You don't think Connie's alive.
你不觉得康妮还活着
You just can't accept what it means if she's not.
你只是无法接受她的死所带来的后果
Well, you're Connie's family.
你是康妮的家人
I would think you'd want to know either way.
我以为你想知道她的生死
I want my family to heal.
我希望我的家人能走出来
All that's left of it.
仅剩的家人
Kelly looks up to you.
凯利仰慕你
Carol, I'm sorry for whatever you're going through,
卡萝尔  我对你所经历的一切很抱歉
but I'm asking you, I'm begging you,
但我想请你  我求求你
whatever you are doing or telling her, stop.
不管你在做什么或对她说什么  停下吧
You're just making it harder.
你让一切变得更难了
Come on, buddy.
走吧  朋友
There you go.
好了
Go on.
吃吧
No, thank you.
不  谢了
Just take really small bites.
一次咬一小口
The smaller, the better.
越小越好
You've eaten it before?
你以前吃过吗
Yeah, on the road, with my mom.
嗯  跟我妈妈漂泊时吃过
You eat what you find.
找到什么吃什么
You ever been on the road?
你漂泊过吗
Not like that.
没像那样漂泊过
Well, you meet a lot of different people.
你能遇到很多不同的人
Just chew it fast.
快点嚼
It's not that bad.
没那么难吃
Not like the spiders.
没蜘蛛难吃
Wanna see if we can pet a pony?
想不想摸小马
Look.
看
They're interested.
它们有兴趣
Do you want to pet a pony?
你想摸小马吗
Beautiful, right? Look. Look.
很漂亮吧  快看
Ready?
好了吗
Goddamn shit.
真他妈恶心
What?
怎么
You like the taste of crap cardboard?
你喜欢吃烂纸板吗
We should get back in the woods.
我们应该回到树林里
The road is faster.
走大路更快
He's right. The woods have cover. It's safer.
他说得对  树林里有掩护  更安全
Let's go there.
我们去那里
No.
不
We need to keep moving.
我们得继续前进
No, we need a break.
不  我们得休息
We'll rest here for a while, and then we'll head out.
我们在这里休息一下  然后出发
I know what you're thinking.
我知道你在想什么
The answer is no.
回答是不行
He's right, Maggie.
他是对的  玛姬
I'm slowing you down.
我拖累你们了
Nope.
不
We're fine.
没事的
Maybe now.
也许现在没事
If these guys are anything like you say they are,
如果那些人和你所说的一样
then it's gonna get worse.
情况就会变得更糟
I'm dead weight.
我是个累赘
We all know it.
我们都知道
We'll help you.
我们会帮你的
You wanna know why I walked away from him...
你想知道我为什么离开了他
and everything he stood for...
和他所代表的一切
joined up with you?
加入了你吗
It's 'cause I trust you...
因为我信任你
to do the right thing.
能做正确的事
No matter how hard it is or how much it costs you.
不管有多难  要付出多大代价
The supplies -- Maggie, look at me.
补给  玛姬  看着我
The supplies are the only thing that matters now.
补给是现在唯一重要的事
Alexandria needs us to do this.
亚历山大需要我们取回补给
They're waiting for us.
他们在等着我们
Hershel and Judith.
赫谢尔和朱迪思
Adam...
亚当
And Adam needs a father.
亚当需要一个父亲
You think I'm gonna make it out of that town alive like this?
你觉得我这样能活着离开那个镇子吗
You left Gage. Leave me.
你丢下了盖奇  也丢下我吧
Gage made his choice.
盖奇做出了选择
And I'm making mine.
我也做出了选择
No.
不
Just...
就...
Maggie, if this plan fails...
玛姬  如果这个计划失败了
then everything you've worked for,
那你所为之奋斗的一切
everything you want for the future,
你对未来的一切愿景
it dies with it.
都会破灭
And then what happens to Adam?
然后亚当会怎样呢
Okay.
好吧
It's not that simple.
没那么简单
Yeah, it is.
就这么简单
The sun is going down.
太阳要下山了
Maggie...
玛姬
you have to make a decision.
你必须做出选择
It's easy for you, isn't it?
对你来说很简单吧
Being reckless with somebody else's life.
全然不顾别人的性命
But you don't get to decide who lives and who dies anymore.
但别人的生死现在不由你决定了
It's your fault.
这是你的错
That we're here.
我们变成这样
Because you destroyed everything that we built.
因为你毁掉了我们所建立的一切
You still have to decide.
你依然要做出决定
Ma-- Maggie.
玛姬
Here.
给
You better be here when we get back.
等我们回来时  你最好还在这里
You better come back.
你们最好能回来